<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TMNT</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="turtle_prompt">Choose a turtle</string>

    <string name="leo_text">The leader of the Turtles. Leonardo aspires to be a brave,
        decisive, perfect hero. Unfortunately, he\'s an inexperienced teen (for the moment at least)
        with three smart-aleck brothers. It\'s the gap between his aspiration and current situation
        that is the greatest source of frustration in Leo\'s life. He\'s the most driven of the four
        Turtles, training and studying relentlessly. He tends to be hard on himself, but his diligence
        does not go unnoticed; he is the favored student of Splinter,
        whose approval he very much craves.</string>



    <string name="mike_text">Physically the smallest of the Turtles and the least mature.
        Mikey is easily distracted and enthusiastic about... well, pretty much everything. He\'s
        also extremely creative. He has a thousand ideas, and every now and then, one of them
        will be brilliant. This combination of creativity and lack of focus gives him a kind
        of "flow" that the other Turtles cannot match. He\'s a social animal (well, mutant), and
        more than the others, begs to be part of the real world.</string>




    <string name="don_text">Donatello is the team inventor and weaponeer. He creates all of their
        gadgets from the simplest bo-staff to their incredible vehicles. He\'s utterly brilliant,
        able to cobble together fantastic stuff from things he\'s literally scrounged from a trash
        heap. He\'s obsessively detail-oriented and often impatient that his brothers can\'t keep up
        with him intellectually. But Donnie also happens to be the most reclusive and socially
        awkward of the Turtles - especially when April is on her way!</string>




    <string name="raph_text">Raphael is the most violent of the four brothers.
        A straight-up brawler, he has very little patience for things like stealth,
        hiding in shadows, or keeping his voice down. While he\'s fiercely loyal to his brothers,
        he\'s also often the one giving them a hard time. Raphael is also the one most likely
        to strike out on his own when he feels slighted or under-appreciated. His closest
        confidante was his pet turtle named Spike. Raphael\'s temper can get the better of him,
        causing him to get into situations over his head.</string>


    <string-array name="turtles">

        <item>Leonardo</item>
        <item>Raphael</item>
        <item>Donatello</item>
        <item>Michelangelo</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
